BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- External, 1936-1981, undated; 3
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1970-1977 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Women, 1961-1975 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - American Bankers Association, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - American Bar Association, 1963-1970 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - American Cancer Society, 1960-1976 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - American Casualty Company, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - American Chemical Society, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1964-1969 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - American College Bureau, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - American College Testing Program, 1961-1974 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1960-1965 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1974-1977 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1978 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education (ACE), 1979-1980 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - The American Educational Complex, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - American Educational Life Insurance Company, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - American Educational Theatre Association, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - American Friends of Wilton Park, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - American Geological Institute, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - American GI Forum of Texas, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - American Good Government Society, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - American Heart Association, 1963-1973 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - American Ideals Conference, 1958-1961 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - American Income Life Insurance Company, 1964-1979 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - American Institute for Foreign Trade, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - American International Investment Corporation, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - American Judicature Society, 1963-1970 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - American Legion, 1968-1969 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - American Men of Science, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - American Negro Commemorative Society, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - American Oil Foundation, 1968 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - American Ordnance Association, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - American Professors for Peace in the Middle East, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - American Protestant Hospital Association, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - American Psychological Association, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - American Psychological Association (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - American Psychological Association (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - American Publishers, Inc., 1973 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - American Red Cross, 1960-1962 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - American Rocket Society, Inc., 1962 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - The American Scholar, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - American Security Council, 1964-1978 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - American Society for Technion, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - American Technological University, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - American Telephone and Telegram Company (AT&T), 1966-1974 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - American Trust Life Insurance Company, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - American United Life Insurance Company, 1963-1969 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - American United Products Corporation, 1969-1970 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - American University, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Amoco Foundation, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - AMTRAK, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Anatomical Board of the State of Texas, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Anderson College, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Andrews University, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Angelo State University, 1971-1976 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Annual Fellowship Competition of the Printing and Publishing Industry, 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1963-1966 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Annuity Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), 1968 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), 1973 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT) (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT) (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT) (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT) (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT) (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - The Anti-Crime Council of Texas (ACT), undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - ARA-Slater School and College Services, 1969-1977 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Arcadia Book Shop, 1965-1968 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Area and Association Missions, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Arizona Southern Baptist Convention, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, 1962-1964 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Arkansas Opportunity Fund, 1964-1969 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Arkwright Mutual Insurance Company, 1963-1966 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Army (U.S.), 1966-1979 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Army (U.S.)-Baylor Alumni Association, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Army Corps of Engineers, 1966-1975 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Andersen and Company, 1964-1975 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Arthur Vining Davis Foundations, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Articles, 1959-1963 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Associated Baptist Colleges of Texas, 1967-1971 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Associated Press Sports Editors, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Association for Higher Education, 1961-1975 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Association of American Colleges (1 of 3), 1960-1980 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Association of American Colleges (2 of 3), 1960-1980 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Association of American Colleges (3 of 3), 1960-1980 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Association of American Law Schools, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1964-1980 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Association of California State University Professors, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Association of Catholic Colleges and Universities, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL), 1961 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities for International-Intercultural Studies (ACUIIS) (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1964-1979 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities of Texas, 1964-1978 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Association of Independent Students of Texas, 1976-1978 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Association of National Advertisers, Inc., 1962 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Association of Schools of Allied Health Professions, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Association of Southern Baptist Colleges and Schools, 1964-1979 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities-Bylaws, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1960-1967, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1968 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1969 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1970-1974 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Association of Texas Colleges and Universities (ATCU), 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1960-1965 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Auburn University, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - August Becker Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Austin Baylor Club, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Austin College, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Austin Community College, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Austin Contracting Company, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Austin Savings and Loans, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1969-1971 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Avery R. Downing Scholarship Fund, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - B Cross-Reference Sheets, 1964-1974, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Balflour Company, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Ball State University, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - BankPac, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Bible Institute, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Children’s Homes, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Baptist College Administrators, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Convention of New York, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Convention of Pennsylvania, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Education Committee, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Baptist Education Study Talk (BEST) Report, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Executive Board Members, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1966-1968 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1970-1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1976-1977 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1978-1979 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Foundation of Texas, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1959-1962 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1966-1968 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1970-1974 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1975-1976 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas, 1980-1981 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Joint Committee on Public Affairs, 1962-1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Medical Center System, 1970-1972 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Press, 1963-1965 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Baptist Public Relations Association, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Baptist School Administrators, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Baptist Standard, 1960-1963 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Baptist Standard, 1964-1969 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Baptist Standard, 1970-1975 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Baptist Standard, 1976-1981 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Baptist State Convention of North Carolina, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Baptist Students Magazine, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Baptist World Alliance, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Baptist World Conference, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Baraca Bible Class, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Barrington College, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Barron Scholarship Fund, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1959-1964 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1965-1968 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1969-1975 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Baylor-Waco Foundation, 1975-1981 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Beall Chapel Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral and Social Sciences Survey Committee, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Bellaire Baptist Church, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Bellamy Flag Award, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Belmont College, 1975-1980 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Belton High School, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Bemis Company, Inc., 1972 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Ben Gurion University of the Negev, 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Berkey-Colortran, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - B-F-W Construction Company, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Bicentennial Program Texas Colleges and Universities, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Bicentennial Youth Debate, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Bills (Governmental), 1969-1973 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Bing Crosby Youth Fund, 1964-1968 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Biographical Arts Foundation, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Birmingham-Southern College, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Bishop College, 1974-1975 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Bishop College, 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Black Enterprise, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Blakely-Brantiff Foundation (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Blakely-Brantiff Foundation (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Blakely-Brantiff Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Blakely-Brantiff Foundation, 1964-1966 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Blakley Law Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Blinn College, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Bluefield College, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Blue Mountain College, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Blue Ribbon Committee, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Booz, Allen, and Hamilton, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Boston University, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1961-1968 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Brantiff International, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Brazos Electric Power Cooperative, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Brazos Higher Education Authority (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Brazos River Authority, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Brigham Young University, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Brinkerhoff Property, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Bristol Laboratories, 1972-1974 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Bristol-Myers Company, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Broadmoor Baptist Church, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Broadway Baptist Church, 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Brooke Army Medical Center, 1963-1973 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Brookshire Grocery Company, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Brookside Inn, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Brotherhood Commission, 1961-1972 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Brown Lipton Foundation, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Brown Memorial Trust, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Brown & Root, Inc., 1968 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Buckner Baptist Benevolences, 1964-1973 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Bulletin on Public Relations and Development, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1968-1977 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Burlington Industries Foundation, 1964-1974 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Burroughs Corporation, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - C Cross-Reference Sheets, 1959-1977, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Cain Homes, 1964-1968 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Cal-Tex Foundation, 1962-1971 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - California Baptist College, 1964-1980 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - California State University, 1972-1976 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Calvary Baptist Church [Beaumont, TX], 1973-1977 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Cameron Iron Works, Inc., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Campbell College, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Campbellsville College [Faculty/Staff Handbooks], 1976 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1961-1970 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Capital National Bank, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Caritas of Waco, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Carling Brewing Company, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Carnation Company Foundation, 1962-1975 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Commission on Higher Education, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Catholic Clarion Herald [Baylor College of Medicine Aid], 1969 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Central Baptist Church, 1967-1977 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1977-1980 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Central Texas Chapter of Certified Public Accountants, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Central Texas Educational Television Foundation, 1957-1972 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Central Texas Regional Blood Center, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1959-1962 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Chared Corporation, 1967-1970 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Chevrolet Motor Division, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Chevron Oil Company, 1970-1972 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Chicago Youth Week Federation, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Christian College Consortium, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Christians Concerned for Israel, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Christian Education Commission (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Christian Education Commission (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Christian Education Commission (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1974 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Christian Education Commission, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Christian Education Commission — The Development of the Christian Education Program of the Baptist Convention of Texas, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Christian Education Commission — The Future Development of the Christian Education Program of the Baptist Convention of Texas, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Christian Education Commission — Study of Faculty Satisfactions and Dissatisfactions (Texas Baptist Colleges and Universities), 1968 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Christian Education Coordinating Board, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Christian Life Commission, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Christian Life Commission, 1963-1969 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Christian Life Commission, 1970-1973 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Christian Life Commission, 1974-1977 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Christian Life Commission, 1978-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Christian Life Publications, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Christian Maturity Council, 1963-1971 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Christianity Today, 1965-1975 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1971-1977 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Chrysler Corporation Fund, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Church and Grace, 1968-1969 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Church-Related Colleges and Universities in the South, 1970-1977 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Church and State, 1960-1964 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Church and State (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Church and State (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Church and State (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Church and State, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Church and State, 1967-1974 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Cities Service Foundation, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Citizens National Bank of Waco, 1968-1981 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Citizens National Committee for Higher Education, Inc., 1965 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - City Charter Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - City Club, 1963-1969 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - City National Bank, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Civic Garden Club, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Civil Defense, 1963 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Civil Judicial Council, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights, 1968-1979 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights Compliance Report, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1969-1973 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Clark Foundation, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Clarke College, 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Clayton Fund, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Wrecking Company [Demolition of Buildings on Campus], 1974 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Cliff Temple Baptist Church, 1965-1972 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Coca-Cola Company, 1968-1974 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - College Abroad, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - The College Board, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - College Bowl, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - College Day, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1969-1975 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - College Heights Baptist Church, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - College Loyalty Alumni Support Program (CLASP), 1961-1966 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - College Management, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - College of the Southwest, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - College and University Presidents, undated (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - College Work-Study Program, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Colorado Baptist General Convention, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Columbia Baptist Church, 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Columbia University, 1964-1972 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Campus Unrest, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Commission on Educational Policy, 1963-1967 (Box 101, Folder 26)